

# NICOLA KOLLMANN



### **ABOUT ME**

A 24-year-old Banking and Finance graduate with a special interest for corporate finance and research.

A curious mind and the ability to solve complex problems in an analytical way are my strenghts.

Playing football on an international level confirmed my belief that team work is the key to achieve high goals in life.



### **LANGUAGES**

German English Spanish Russian French



## PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Microsoft Office Word, Excel, Power Point, Outlook

Programming Skills LaTex, Stata, R, MatLab

**Teamwork** 

Leadership

Negotiation & presentations ■





Noflerstrasse 28, 9491 Ruggell Principality of Liechtenstein



+ 41 78 903 20 42



View my Linkedin profile

### **EDUCATION**



University of St.Gallen - Switzerland Ph.D in Finance 2019 - Now

- University of St.Gallen Switzerland Master of Arts HSG, Banking and Finance (MBF) 2016 - 2018
- BI Norwegian Business School Oslo, Norway Exchange semester, Finance 2017
- Bachelor of Science (B.sc.), Business Administration

Major: Buiness Administratino (150 ETCS) Minor: Corporate and Civil Law (30 ETCS)

University of Bern - Switzerland

2013 - 2016

#### **EXPERIENCE**



Research Associate University of St. Gallen - Switzerland Oct 2018 - Now

• Business Development Associate Lopag Trust reg. - Ruggell, Liechtenstein Jan 2018 - Jul 2018

Internship in Financial Services Lopag Trust reg. - Ruggell, Liechtenstein Jun 2015 - Nov 2015

Internship in Group Accounting Hilti - Schaan, Liechtenstein Jul 2014 - Sep 2014

### **VOLUNTEERING**



Finimize

Finimize provides people around the world with tools and information to get financially savvy.